We have been talking about how to wear your wigs, how to take care of them, how to store them.
One of the things that I always tell people is if you don't like to wear a cap underneath your wig don't.
There is no right or wrong way to do it.
You know just make sure your hair is neatly tucked in under your wig and play with it.
Some people really need the cap to feel that security that it gives you.
Some people it drives them crazy you know play with it and see what works best for you.
You want to be comfortable, you want to be able to wear your wig and have fun with it and just be comfortable with it.
You don't want it to be a nescient so if the cap is bothering your, if it is making your head feel really tight take it off.
It is not going to make your wig look back, it is not going to hurt it at all.
The cap does help keep your wig clean but it is not necessary.